Finding Aid for High/Scope Educational Research Foundation Records 1963-2000
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- President Records, David P. Weikart
  - Writings and speeches
    - Articles published
      - 1979-1981 (Box 21)
      - 1982-1985 (Box 21)
        lacking 1983
      - 1986 1988 (Box 21)
      - 1989 1991 (Box 21)
      - 1996-1998, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - undated (Box 21)
    - Books
      - Early Schooling: On What Grounds?, 1986-1987 (Box 21)
      - Significant Benefits: The High/Scope Perry Preschool Study Through Age 27, 1993-1994, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Lasting Differences: The High/Scope Preschool Curriculum Comparison Study Through Age 23, 1996-1997 (Box 21)
    - Chapters published
      - A Traditional Nursery Program Revisited, 1972-1973 (Box 21)
      - The High/Scope Cognitively Oriented Curriculum, 1977 (Box 21)
      - Minnesota Symposium on Child Psychology, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
      - Early Academics, 1990 (Box 22)
      - Organizing Principles of the High/Scope Curriculum, 1991 (Box 22)
      - High Scope Preschool Program Outcomes, 1992 (Box 22)
      - The High/Scope Curriculum for Early Childhood Care and Education, 1993 (Box 22)
      - Early Childhood Education, 1993 (Box 22)
      - Early Childhood Education Today, 1994 (Box 22)
      - Primary Prevention Works, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Driving Master Brain, 1996-1997 (Box 22)
    - High/Scope Papers
      - 1966-1970, 2 folders (Box 22)
      - 1978-1979, 1981, 1983 (Box 22)
      - 1985 1987 (Box 22)
      - 1988-1993, 5 folders (Box 22)
      - 1995-1997 (Box 22)
      - undated (Box 22)
    - Speeches and presentations
      - 1966-1969, 2 folders (Box 22)
      - 1971 (Box 22)
      - 1973, 2 folders (Box 22)
      - 1974-1976 (Box 23)
      - 1977 1979 (Box 23)
      - 1980-1991, 16 folders (Box 23)
      - 1992-1997 (Box 23)
        lacking 1993 and 1996
    - Miscellaneous papers
      - 1965-1967 (Box 23)
      - 1972 1974 (Box 23)
      - 1976 (Box 23)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 23)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 23)